我们已经谈到了颜色对人类的重要性，我们有成千上万的颜色
We have talked about how important color is to human beings, that we have thousands of
用词来形容许多不同深浅的色彩。
words to describe many, many different shades of color.
颜色对我们来说显然很重要;它帮助我们在日常生活中能够描述
Color is clearly important to us; it helps us in our everyday life to be able to describe
物体的颜色。
objects by their color.
那么这种颜色概念从何而来？
So where does this concept of color come from?
这个过程的许多部分导致你对颜色的感知
There a number of parts of the process that lead to you having a perception of color in
你的思想和我们要做的是从头到尾经历那些。
your mind and what we are going to do is go through those from the beginning to the end.
在整个过程开始时，我们拥有所谓的光源。
At the start of the whole process we have what we call an illuminant.
光源是发光的东西，光线照在场景上，闪耀着光芒
An illuminant is a thing that emits light and the light shines on the scene, shines
在我们感兴趣的对象上，我们称之为入射光，我们称之为
on the object that we are interested in and we call this incoming light, we call that
照度。
the illuminance.
所以照度是来自光源的光线落在我们感兴趣的物体上
So the illuminance is the light from the illuminant that falls on the object that we are interested
在。
in.
现在，物体反射了一些光和来自物体的光
Now the object reflects some of that light and the light that comes from the object we
我们称之为亮度，我们谈论对象的亮度。
refer to as the luminance, we talk about the luminance of the object.
在这种情况下，我们将参考苹果的亮度，因此光线来自我们的
In this case we would refer to the luminance of the apple, so light is coming in from our
光亮的，撞击苹果，反射它并进入我们观察者的眼睛。
illuminant, striking the apple, reflecting off it and entering the eye of our observer.
一些非常神奇的事情发生在眼睛里面。
Some pretty amazing things happen within the eye.
进入的光子会触发杆的后部和锥形细胞的化学反应
The incoming photons trigger a chemical reaction in the rod and cone cells at the back of your
眼睛。
eye.
它们又导致通过视神经传播的电脉冲
They lead, in turn, to electrical impulses which are transmitted through the optic nerve
到你大脑的视觉皮层，它位于你的脑后，那个
to the visual cortex of your brain, which is located in the back of your head, and that
导致红色的感知。
leads to the perception of the color red.
您将与您正在查看的对象相关联-在这种情况下，苹果。
Which you would associate with the object you are looking at—in this case, the apple.